

JAYSON GARCIA
WEB DEVELOPER

Contact

Blk 23 Lot 19 Brgy. San Lorenzo Ruiz, Taytay Rizal

+639561490771

https://hallowichig0.github.io

garciajayson502@gmail.com

Portfolio

Website:

https://hallowichig0.github.io/#portfolio

GitHub.

https://github.com/hallowichig0

�� Skills

- Drupal (8 & 9)
- Wordpress (Sage, Bedrock & ACF Stoutlogic)
- Laravel
- PHP
- TWIG Template Engine
- Blade Template Engine
- MySQL
- HTML 5
- CSS 3

About Me

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the Information Technology industry.

Skilled in Drupal (8 & 9), Wordpress (Roots Sage 10 + Bedrock + ACF StoutLogic), PHP, Symfony, Twig, Blade, Javascript, Jquery, HTML 5, CSS 3, SCSS, MySQL, Responsive Web Design & Linux.

Strong Backend & Frontend skills with Associates degree focused in Information Technology.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

June 2013 - April 2017 Jose Rizal University

Work Experience

Yondu, Inc.

July 2022 - Present

Software Engineer II

- Integrated cmsable component for New Globe One
- Exposed cmsable component REST API for New Globe One
- Created custom DateTimePicker for cmsable schedule

Halcyon Digital Media Design Inc.

May 2019 - July 2022

Web Developer

- Designed, developed websites based on Adobe XD & Figma mock-up. (Primarily using Drupal, Wordpress, Laravel, PHP, Symfony, TWIG, Blade, HTML 5, CSS 3, SASS, Javascript & MySQL).
- Integrated Custom Theme in every wordpress & drupal projects. (I used my own boilerplate setup).
- Integrated sage 10 theme & bedrock in all wordpress projects.
- Used composer tool, npm, yarn & gulp js to manage the plugins/modules & libraries dependencies.
- Used Git and GitHub to make the creation of the website more centralized and organized.

- SCSS
- Javascript
- jQuery
- React JS / Next JS
- Git
- GitHub / GitLab / Bitbucket
- Composer / NPM / Yarn
- Webpack
- Laravel Mix
- Gulp JS
- Linux / Bash / Shell Scripting

Evervue Philippines Inc.

September 2018 - March 2019

Web Developer

- Designed, developed websites. (Primarily using WORDPRESS, HTML, CSS, SASS, PHP, JAVASCRIPT & MYSQL).
- Designed and programmmed online e-commerce and commercial website for electronic product of Evervue Philippines Inc.
- Integrated Custom Theme Backend. Used Git and GitLab to make the creation of the website more centralized and organized.
- Resolved program error and other technical issues by leveraging strengths in coding, debugging and integration testing.
- Supported users in managing, maintaining, access server and troubleshooting for both local area networks and hardware.
- Set up equipment for employees, including installing TCP/IP, cables, software and hardware.

GlobeTek Science Foundation Inc.

April 2017- August 2018

Web Developer

- Designed, developed websites. (Primarily using HTML, CSS, PHP, JAVASCRIPT, MYSQL & WORDPRESS).
- Designed and programmed online e-commerce website for both retail product and online restaurant for GlobeTek Science Foundation Inc.
- Designed and programmed mobile application for the Earth Fashion Café online restaurant.
- Programmed E-Learning System for the school to view both the grades and files of both the students and teachers. The teacher could input the grades of each students in into system.
- Resolved program error and other technical issues by leveraging strengths in coding, debugging and integration testing.
- Structure and 3D modeling of store replica and schematics using sketch up.